Warren S. McCulloch Papers 1860s-1987 Mss.B.M139
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1931-1968; 13.5 lin. feet (Box 1-28)
  - Sheckers, G. Dale, 1963; 2 items
  - Shedlovsky, Theldore, 1946-1951; 6 items
  - Sheehan, Donal, 1948; 2 items
  - Sheffler, Thomas B., 1967-1968; 4 items
  - Sheil School of Social Studies, 1947; 1 item
  - Shellow, James M., 1949-1951; 9 items
  - Shepard Laboratories, 1955; 1 item
  - Sheps, Cecil G., 1959; 1 item
  - Sherrer, Jean, 1959; 1 item
  - Sherwood, Stephen L., 1953-1969; 9 folders
  - Shilling, Charles W., 1953-1969; 5 items
  - Shiman, Paul L., 1961; 1 item
  - Shirley, Hunter B., 1967; 3 items
  - Sholl, Donald A., 1951-1957; 7 items
  - Shuman, Stanley S., 1960; 1 item
  - Shurcliff, William A., 1964; 4 items
  - Shurrager, Phil S., 1960-1962; 3 items
  - Sichel, Elsa Keil, 1968; 3 items
  - Siewers, Anne, 1645-1949; 3 items
  - Sigma Xi. Loyola University, 1957; 4 items
  - Sigma Xi. Northwestern University, 1953-1955; 2 items
  - Sigma Xi. University of Massachusetts, 1957-1961; 2 items
  - Silbergeld, Samuel, 1945-1955; 15 items
  - Silveira, Anibal, 1942-1945; 2 items
  - Silver, Alene F., 1963; 7 items
  - Silver, Maurice L., 1948-1963; 25 items
  - Silverstein, Joe, n.d.; 1 item
  - Siminoff, Robert, 1968; 1 item
  - Simmel, Marianne, 1950-1954; 12 items
  - Simmons, Vaughan P., 1946; 1 item
  - Simons, David G., n.d.; 1 item
  - Simpson, Robert M., 1960; 2 items
  - Singer, Milton, 1949; 2 items
  - Sitter, Stephen C., 1947-1951; 6 items
  - Sizer, Irwin W., 1956-1957; 2 items
  - Skandamis, Leon N., 1948; 2 items
  - Skeffington, A. M., 1961; 1 item
  - Sklodowski-Ordon, Vladimir, 1965; 4 items
  - Slamecka, Vladimir, 1969; 1 item
  - Slater, Lloyd E., 1958-1966; 37 items
  - Slater, Lloyd E. and The Bioinstrumentation Advisory Council, 1966; 3 items
  - Smagala, Joseph R., 1968; 2 items
  - Smetters, George W., 1955; 7 items
  - Smith, Arthur M., 1961; 1 item
  - Smith, Caldwell P., 1957; 1 item
  - Smith, Cedric M., 1958; 1 item
  - Smith, Homer, 1969; 1 item
  - Smith, Robert A., 1966; 1 item
  - Smythies, J. R., 1955-1967; 11 item
  - Snider, Ray S., 1947-1958; 4 items
  - Snieler, Ray, 1947-1958; 4 items
  - Sociedad Espanola de Cibernetica, n.d.; 1 item
  - Society for General Systems Research, n.d.; 2 items
  - Socoloff, Eli B., 1954-1955; 14 items
  - Soell, Mrs. Janet Sprague, 1948; 3 items
  - Sokolov, 1965; 6 items
  - Solomon, Harry C., 1953-1954; 2 items
  - Solomon, Philip, 1958; 2 items
  - Solow, Herbert, 1963; 1 item
  - Sommer, Conrad, 1943; 2 items
  - Sommerhoff, G., 1962; 1 item
  - Sonnenschein, R. R, 1953-1955; 3 items
  - Soriano, Victor, 1960; 2 items
  - Soulairac, A., 1950; 2 items
  - Southwestern Congress of Optometry, 1951; 2 items
  - Sparkes, John J., 1965; 1 item
  - Speck, Ross V., 1965-1966; 2 items
  - Spence, Harry, n.d.; 1 item
  - Sperry, Albert F., 1960; 2 items
  - Spiegel, E., 1960; 2 items
  - Spiegel, Leo A., 1945; 2 items
  - Spinks, A., 1958; 1 item
  - Sponga, Imre, 1963; 3 items
  - Sprague, James M., 1951; 4 items
  - Sprague, R. E., 1953; 1 item
  - Springer, George F., 1965; 4 items
  - Springer, Publishing Co., Inc., 1961; 5 items
  - Springer-Verlag, 1966-1968; 8 items
  - Spurling, R. Glen, 1947; 2 items
  - Stahl, Walter R., 1961-1966; 52 items
  - Stahlman, William D., 1948; 2 items
  - Stark, David T., 1962; 4 items
  - Stark, Lawrence, 1951-1969; 23 items
  - Starr, James H., 1947; 3 items
  - Stechert-Shafner Inc., 1966; 3 items
  - Steel, Van H., 1962; 9 items
  - Steele, Jack E., 1960-1961; 7 items
  - Steen, Lynn A., 1959; 2 items
  - Steggerda, F. R., 1945-1947; 7 items
  - Steiger, Fred C., 1963; 2 items
  - Stein, Samuel I., 1946-1957; 4 items
  - Stein, Seymour N., 1952-1965; 19 items
  - Steinberg, J. C., 1950; 2 items
  - Steinfeld, Julius I., 1952; 4 items
  - Stelter, Agnes, 1958; 1 item
  - Stevenson, Ian, 1954; 1 item
  - Stephenson, John Leslie, 1947-1959; 6 items
  - Sterling, Theodor D., 1967; 1 item
  - Stern, Alexander W., 1961; 1 item
  - Stevens, John, 1949(?); 1 item
  - Stewart, John L., 1963; 1 item
  - Stewart, Robert M., 1962-1965; 4 items
  - Still, Joseph W., 1965; 2 items
  - Stokes, Aldwyn, 1952-1968; 7 items
  - Stone, Frederick L., 1954; 1 item
  - Stone, William E. W., 1939-1951; 45 items
  - Storm, van Leeuwen, Willem, 1962; 7 items
  - Strackee, Jan Stratton, Henry M., 1961-1969; 2 items
  - Stratton, Henry M., 1945-1949; 6 items
  - Straus, Erwin W., 1954; 3 items
  - Strauss, Richard, 1948; 1 item
  - Stroud, John M., 1948-1951; 28 items
  - Struven, D. J., 1952; 2 items
  - Struthers, R. R, 1949; 1 item
  - Stuck, H. C., 1943; 2 items
  - Sturgis, Sullivan Warren, 1952; 3 items
  - Subirana, A., 1951; 2 items
  - Sunderland, Sydney, 1949; 1 item
  - Sutherland, Ivan E., 1959; 3 items
  - Sutro, Louis, 1963-1969; 23 items
  - Svaetichin, Gunnar, 1960; 3 items
  - Svoboda, Frantisek, 1966; 5 items
  - Swanson, Rowena. U. S. Air Force Office. Office of Scientific Research, 1962-1967; 58 items
  - Sweeney, Myrtle, 1960; 1 item
  - Sweet, William H., 1947-1948; 5 items
  - Syracuse University, 1964-1965; 4 items
  - Syracuse Psychopathic Hospital, 1946; 1 item
  - Szafranski, Peter, 1968; 2 items
  - Székely, D. L., 1964-1965; 2 items
  - Takagi, Sadayuki, 1953; 7 items
  - Takats, G. de, 1948; 1 item
  - Taketomo, Yasuhiko, 1960-1962; 6 items
  - Talbot, David T., 1948; 3 items
  - Talbot, Samuel A., 1938-1948; 5 items
  - Tangen, John N., 1962; 1 item
  - Tannenbaum, Jerome, 1945-1949; 3 items
  - Tanner, Spike, 1961; 1 item
  - Taschdjian, Edgar, 1939-1968; 2 items
  - Taub, Abraham, 1948-1951; 7 items
  - Taub, Arthur H., 1862-1968; 8 items
  - Taubes, Jacob, 1954; 3 items
  - Tausig, Theodore, 1954-1968; 24 items
  - Taylor, A. B., 1945-1948; 4 items
  - Taylor, Reginald, 1941-1952; 17 items
  - Teagle, Walter C., 1951-1952; 4 items
  - Technology Review, 1962-1967; 4 items
  - Teller, Edward, 1969; 1 item
  - Ten Hoopen, Ir. Marinus, 1958-1960; 10 items
  - Terra, Eleanor de, 1943; 1 item
  - Terrills, M. W., 1955; 1 item
  - Terry, R. A., 1962; 2 items
  - Teuber, Hans Lukas, 1950-1964; 3 items
  - Texas Instruments, Inc., 1960-1962; 10 items
  - Thayer, Lee O., 1968-1969; 9 items
  - Thayer, Nancy, 1966; 4 items
  - Theodore, James J., 1947-1948; 2 items
  - Theodosis, Steven D., 1965-1966; 2 items
  - Thiess, Frank B., 1959; 7 items
  - Thomas, Berger, 1952-1954; 4 items
  - Thomas, C. D., 1954; 1 item
  - Thomas, Charles C., 1942-1961; 55 items
  - Thomas, George B., Jr., 1967; 1 item
  - Thomas, Henry Bascom, 1943; 1 item
  - Thomas, L. B., 1951; 3 items
  - Thomas, William Owen, 1944-1950; 5 items
  - Thrope, G. G, 1966; 1 item
  - Thrope, W. H., 1951; 1 item
  - Thurstone, L. L, 1947; 1 item
  - Tietz, John W., 1947; 1 item
  - Tingle, Leonard, 1945; 1 item
  - Tinker, Alan J., 1945; 2 items
  - Tislow, Richard F., 1962; 1 item
  - Tobias, Julian, 148-1956; 11 item
  - Tobin, Michael W., 1950; 2 items
  - Toman, John, 1946-1950; 15 items
  - Tönnies, J. F., 1948-1954; 9 items
  - Toman, James E. P., 1938; 1 item
  - Tompkins, Howard E., 1955-1960; 7 items
  - Tower, Sarah, 1942; 3 items
  - Transducer Corporation, 1951-1952; 5 items
  - Trautman, De Forest L., 1954; 1 item
  - Trurnit, Hans J., 1950; 8 items
  - Tschaler, Jean Pierre, 1963; 1 item
  - Tucker, Don, 1955; 2 items
  - Tulane University, 1946; 1 item
  - Tunnell, Daniel R., 1963; 1 item
  - Tunturi, Archie R., 1953-1954; 4 items
  - Turner, William J., 1951-1957; 2 items
  - Tykociner, J. T., 1951; 2 items
  - Tyler, David B., 1969; 3 items
  - Uhr, Leonard, 1964; 2 items
  - Ullman, Momtague, 1964; 4 items
  - United Cerebral Palsy Assoc., Inc., 1951; 2 items
  - Unidentified, n.d.; 1 item
  - United States. Air Force Avionics Laboratory, 1964-1965; 3 items
  - United States. Air Force Cambridge Research Laboratories, 1963; 2 items
  - United States. Air Force Office of Scientific Research, 1949-1967; 14 items
  - United States. School of Aerospace Medicine, 1961-1966; 13 items
  - United States. Army Medical Service Graduate School. Medical Basic Sciences Course, 1947-1953; 119 items
  - United States. Army Medical Division, 1947-1949; 49 items
  - United States. Armed Forces Insittute of Pathology, 1949; 3 items
  - United States. Atomic Energy Commission, 1950; 1 item
  - United States. Dept. of Commerce. U. S. Patent Office, -1962; 2 items
  - United States. Dept. of Commerce. National Bureau of Standards, 1955-1967; 3 items
  - United States. Dept. of Health, Education. and Welfare. National Institutes of Health, 1951-1961; 9 items
  - United States. Navy. Office of Naval Research, 1951-1961; 9 items
  - United States. Federal Security Agency. Public Health Service, 1948-1952; 17 items
  - United States. Naval Medical Research Laboratory, 1948-1952; 38 items
  - United States. Veterans Administration. Washington, D. C., 1946-1950; 7 items
  - United States. Veterans Administration. Augusta, Georgia, 1950-1951; 6 items
  - United States. Veterans Administration. Illinois, 1950; 5 items
  - United States. Veterans Administration. Kansas, 1951; 3 items
  - United States. Veterans Administration. Maryland, 1954-1966; 13 items
  - United States. Veterans Administration. New York, 1949; 1 item
  - United States. Veterans Administration. Washington (state), 1951; 5 items
  - United States Trust Co., 1961; 1 item
  - Unna, Klaus, 1949; 2 items
  - University of California Medical Center, 1959-1964; 2 items
  - University of Chicago, 1966; 1 item
  - University of Chicago. Research Committee, 1948-1962; 3 items
  - University of Chicago Press, 1950-1952; 5 items
  - University of Chicago Psychology Club, n.d.; 2 items
  - University of Colorado, 1966; 1 item
  - University of Denver, 1961; 1 item
  - University of Denver. Denver Research Institute, 1958; 1 item
  - University of Florida, 1962-1967; 2 items
  - University of Hawaii, 1968; 1 item
  - University of Illinois, 1948-1964; 8 items
  - University of Illinois. Animal Hospital, 1948; 4 items
  - University of Illinois College of Engineering, 1952; 4 items
  - University of Illinois College of Medicine, 1949; 4 items
  - University of Illinois College of Medicine. Committee on Care of Equipment of Classrooms, 1948; 7 items
  - University of Illinois Committee on Instruction, 1951; 2 items
  - University of Illinois Committee on University Statutes, 1950; 4 items
  - University of Illinois Graduate School, 1947-1953; 45 items
  - University of Illinois Physical Plant, 1945-1948; 3 items
  - University of Illinois Public Information, 1943-1952; 15 items
  - University of Kansas, 1962; 1 item
  - University of Kentucky, 1962; 1 item
  - University of Missouri, 1964-1965; 2 items
  - University of North Carolina. Institute of Statics, 1962-1965; 8 items
  - University of Pittsburg. School of Engineering, 1957; 3 items
  - University of Pittsburg. School of Medicine, 1953-1961; 8 items
  - University of Puerto Rico. School of Medicine, 1957-1958; 4 items
  - University of Rochester, 1960-1961; 3 items
  - University of Sussex, 1964; 3 items
  - University of Texas, 1968; 1 item
  - University of Texas: Conference on Vision, color, design, 1955; 1 item
  - University of Waterloo, 1965; 1 item
  - University of Wisconsin. Environmental Design Center, 1964-1967; 5 items
  - Unknown, 1955-1969; 8 items
  - Unna, Klaus R., 1952; 1 item
  - Uttley, Albert M., 1961-1964; 16 items
  - Van Atta, Lester C., 1965; 2 items
  - Van Dam, 1960; 2 items
  - Van de Grind, W. A., 1967; 1 item
  - Vanderbilt University, 1961-1962; 5 items
  - Van der Horst, L., 1948-1949; 2 items
  - Van der Kraan, Piet, 1963; 2 items
  - Vander Reis, Leo, 1950; 6 items
  - Van der Tweel, Louis Hendrik, 1949-1966; 58 items
  - Van Dixhoorn, J. J, 1964; 3 items
  - Van Eick, A. J., 1961; 2 items
  - Van Gorcum. Koninklijke van Gorcum en Co., 1967; 1 item
  - Van Lith, Paul, 1967; 1 item
  - Van Soest, J. L., 1962; 1 item
  - Van Weele, Marinus H., 1963; 1 item
  - Vasiloff, Alexander, 1954-1960; 3 items
  - Veith Ilza, 1951-1952; 5 items
  - Verbeek, Leo A. M., 1958-1968; 23 items
  - Ver Brugghen, Adrien, 1966-1967; 2 items
  - Verhaart, W. J. C., 1949-1953; 2 items
  - Verveen, Alettus Albertinus, 1960-1968; 29 items
  - Verzeand, Marcel, 1951; 1 item
  - Vista Laboratory, 1964; 4 items
  - Vlieger, M. de, 1965-1966; 18 items
  - Voevodsky, John, 1949-1962; 10 items
  - von Domarus, Walter Eilhard Alfred, 1948-1950; 7 items
  - Von Foerster, Heinz, 1948-1968; 65 item
  - Von Neumann, John, 1949-1955; 15 items
  - Vries, Hugo de, 1951; 4 items
  - Wainio, Walter W., 1948; 3 items
  - Wakefield, A. F., 1953-1956; 2 items
  - Wakerlin, George E., 1947-1952; 6 items
  - Walker, A. Earl, 1947-1953; 9 items
  - Wall, Patrick, 1949-1965; 11 item
  - Walls, Gordon, 1951; 5 items
  - Walshe, F. M. R., 1951; 7 items
  - Walshe, Francis M. R., 1932-1959; 5 items
  - Walsh, Patrick J., 1967; 7 items
  - Walter, W. Grey, 1947-1960; 19 items
  - Walther, A., 1958; 4 items
  - Wang, Richard I. H., 1952; 2 items
  - Ward, Arthur A., Jr., 1941-1952; 106 items
  - Ward, Raymond P., 1954; 1 item
  - Warner, F. J., 1947; 2 items
  - Warren, Richard E., 1964-1965; 4 items
  - Warren, Stafford L., 1949-1966; 5 items
  - Washington, Lamar, 1964; 1 item
  - Watson, James W., 1951; 3 items
  - Waverly Press Inc., 1947-1948; 4 items
  - Webb, Donald R., 1963; 1 item
  - Weber, Robert E., 1963; 1 item
  - Wechsler, Richard, 1954; 2 items
  - Weedon, W. S., 1960-1961; 4 items
  - Weimer, Paul K., 1958; 1 item
  - Weinberg, Alvin M., 1950; 1 item
  - Weinberger, Walter, 1950; 2 items
  - Weinstein, Stanley, 1959; 1 item
  - Weir, Homer, n.d.; 1 item
  - Wells, Oliver D., 1960-1968; 10 items
  - Wells, Robert, 1965; 1 item
  - Wendt, G. R., 1947; 9 items
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anthropological Research, 1969; 1 item
  - Wesleyan University, 1961; 2 items
  - West, D. C., 1967; 1 item
  - West, Jan C., 1968; 5 items
  - Westcott, J. H., 1948; 1 item
  - Western Reserve University, 1963; 2 items
  - Weshtinghouse Electric Company, 1967-1968; 4 items
  - Wexler, Richard, 1947-1950; 4 items
  - Wheatley, Max D., 1944-1959; 31 item
  - Wheeler, David J., 1952; 1 item
  - Whieldon, John A., 1947-1951; 10 items
  - White, Denis, 1950-1953; 4 items
  - White, G., Jr., 1955; 3 items
  - White House. Executive Office of the President. Office of Science and Technology, 1961-1963; 15 items
  - Whitman, C. Lewis, 1964; 3 items
  - Whitmore, William F., 1965-1966; 4 items
  - Who's Important in Medicine, 1950; 3 items
  - Who's Who, Inc., 1958-1964; 4 items
  - Who's Who in American Education, Inc, 1950; 3 items
  - Whyte, Lancelot Law, 1949; 1 item
  - Wiener, Norbert, 1947-1962; 4 items
  - Wiersma, C. A. G., 1963-1964; 2 items
  - Wiesner, Jerome, 1950-1958; 6 items
  - Wiggers, Harold C., 1950; 1 item
  - Wikler, Abraham, 1944-1954; 28 items
  - Wilcox, Paul H., 1949-1950; 3 items
  - Wilhelm, R. H., 1967; 3 items
  - Willard, A. C., 1942-1946; 3 items
  - Williams, Curtis A., 1967; 2 items
  - Williams, J. D., 1959; 1 item
  - Williams and Wilkins Co., 1950; 2 items
  - Williamson, Robert R., 1949; 2 items
  - Willis, David G., 1958-1962; 3 items
  - Willis, Paul A., 1960; 1 item
  - Willner, Otto, 1943; 2 items
  - Wilson, Mrs. Clifton T., 1950; 1 item
  - Wilson, Edwin B., 1954-1964; 9 items
  - Wilson, Vernon E., 1965; 1 item
  - Winder, Robert O., 1962; 2 items
  - Windle, William F., 1944; 1 item
  - Wing, Kenneth R., 1961; 2 items
  - Winograd, Samuel, 1961-1963; 9 items
  - Winternitz, M. C., 1944; 2 items
  - Wisdom, J. O., 1953; 2 items
  - Wittenberger, 1958; 1 item
  - Wolbarsht, M. L., 1966; 1 item
  - Wolf, Abner, 1943; 1 item
  - Wolken, Jerome J., 1957-1967; 50 items
  - Wong, Harry Y. C., 1960; 3 items
  - Woodard, Geoffrey, 1948; 4 items
  - Woodbury, Lowell A., 147-1949; 8 items
  - Woolsey, Clinton N., 1941-152; 12 items
  - World Biography, 1952; 3 items
  - Wortis, S. Bernard, 1931-1964; 16 items
  - Woudhuysen, H. L., 1965-1966; 2 items
  - VonWright, Georg Henirk, 1964; 1 item
  - Wright, Jain Lee, 1963; 2 items
  - Wright, Samson, 1946; 1 item
  - Wulff, V. J., 1948; 1 item
  - Wyke, Barry, 1948; 1 item
  - Wylie, Ruth C., 1951; 2 items
  - Wymore, A. Wayne, 1960; 3 items
  - Wyss, Oscar A. M., 1947; 2 items
  - Yahn, George, 1961; 1 item
  - Yakovlev, Paul I., 1947-1955; 6 items
  - Yale University, 1949-1962; 3 items
  - Yale University -- Alumni Fund, 1953-1966; 3 items
  - Yale University. Office of the Registrar, 1948; 1 item
  - Yale University. School of Art and Architecture, 1969; 2 items
  - Yamanoto, Toshio, 1964; 2 items
  - Yanins, David M., 1949; 1 item
  - Yanowsky, Nicholas, 1968; 1 item
  - Yates, F. Eugene, 1965; 3 items
  - Ycas, Martynas, 1961-1966; 4 items
  - Yeager, J. Franklin, 1949; 8 items
  - Yerkes, Robert M., 1940; 1 item
  - Yilmaz, Huseyin, 1940; 1 item
  - Yngve, Victor, 1958; 2 items
  - Yockey, Hubert P., 1956; 3 items
  - Yoffey, J. M., 1943; 1 item
  - Youmans, John B., 1947-1949; 8 items
  - Young, James R., 1969; 1 item
  - Young, Lewis H., 1960; 1 item
  - Yovitz, Marshall C., 1958-1961; 12 items
  - Ypsilanti (Mich.) State Hospital, 1962; 2 items
  - Zacharias, Jerrold R., 1956; 1 item
  - Zackay, Victor F., 1968-1969; 2 items
  - Zangwill, O. L., 1949-1952; 4 items
  - Zeisler, Ernest B., 1950-1951; 3 items
  - Zeitlin, Jacob, 1948; 1 item
  - Zeleznik, Carter, 1958-1968; 71 item
  - Zenith Radio Corp., 1948; 1 item
  - Zetterberg, Lars H., 1968; 4 items
  - Ziegler, Victor, 1932-1938; 11 item
  - Zopf, George Walter, Jr., 1958-1965; 17 items
  - Zorbaugh, Harvey, 1948; 2 items
  - Zotterman, Y., 1957; 1 item
  - Zweighaft, James F. B., 1948-1949; 2 items
- Series II. Professional Papers, 1939-1970; 33 lin. feet (Box 29-61)
  Material relating primarily to McCulloch's participation in conferences and associtations, but also containing correspondence.
  - Abstract reviews of current Soviet Space literature, 1961-1965; 2 items
  - Academic Laboratory staff, 1941-1943; 1 item
  - ACTH, 1949; 1 item
  - Aeromedical and physical environment laboratory. Progress report, no.5., 1950-1951; 2 items
  - Aeromedical evaluation record, 1960-1961; 1 item
  - Aerospace medical association, 1965-1968; 16 items
  - Albert Einstein College of Medicine, 1959-1960; 10 items
  - Albert Lundy Baker Foundation #1, 1965; 8 items
  - Albert Lundy Baker Foundation #2, 1965; 4 items
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1957-1969; 7 items
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1969; 4 items
    Includes certificate of membership
  - American Association of Anatomists, 1945-1952; 24 items
  - American Institute of Electrical Engineers #1, 1949-1951; 27 items
  - American Institute of Electrical Engineers #2, 1948-1948; 38 items
  - American Institute of Electrical Engineers #3, 1946-1948; 31 item
  - American League against Epilepsy [and] American Branch of the International League Against Epilepsy, 1942-1950; 9 items
  - American Medical Association, 1946-1962; 12 items
  - American Neurological Association #1, 1943-1948; 31 item
  - American Neurological Association #2, 1949; 28 items
  - American Neurological Association #3, 1950; 20 items
  - American Neurological Association #4, 1951-1952; 18 items
  - American Neurological Association #5, 1955-1969; 10 items
  - American Neurological Association #6, 1952-1964; 11 item
  - American Neurological Association #7, 1954-1963; 4 items
  - American Psychiatric Association, 1946-1951; 5 items
  - American Society for Research in Psychosomatic Problems, 1944-1947; 29 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Board meetings. #1, 1966-1969; 19 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Board meetings. #2, 1964-1966; 28 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. By-laws, 1964-1966; 10 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Communications, 1966; 6 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Correspondence #1, 1964-1965; 11 item
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Correspondence #2, 1966-1967; 30 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Correspondence #3, 1968-1969; 29 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Financial #1, 1967-1969; 37 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Financial #2, 1966-1967; 19 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Local chapters #1, 1968-1969; 27 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Local chapters #2, 1965-1966; 10 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Membership list, 1968-1969; 17 items
  - American Society of Cybernetics. Newsletters and publications, 1967-1969; 24 items
  - American Statistical Association, 1947-1948; 7 items
  - Artorga #1, 1960-1961; 32 items
  - Artorga #2, 1961; 8 items
  - Artorga Misc. Issues: Nos. 3 - 39, 1959-1962; 19 items
  - Artorga Misc. Issues: Nos. 40 - 75, 1962-1966; 29 items
  - Association for Computing Machinery, 1948 - 1949, 11 item
  - Association for Computing Machinery, 1950 -, 1949-1952; 14 items
  - Association for Psychodynamics, 1945; 3 items
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease #1, 1953-1963; 21 item
  - Association for Research in Nervous and Mental Disease #2, 46 items
  - Bell, 1954; 1 item
  - Bell Telephone Labs., Inc., 1958; 6 items
  - Bibliography #1, 1963-1969; 6 items
  - Bibliography #2, n.d.; 11 item
  - Bibliography of space medicine, 1958; 1 item
  - Bibliography Publications of Dr. E. Th. v. Brucke, n.d.; 1 item
  - Bioastronautics panel material, 1961; 11 item
  - Biochemical rationale of shock therapy, 1943; 1 item
  - Biomedical engineering society, 1968; 1 item
  - Biometric Society, 1947-1952; 16 items
  - Biomimesis, n.d.; 1 item
  - Bionics, 1965; 2 items
  - Boston Society for Psychiatry and Neurology, 1949; 9 items
  - Brain research and human behavior, 1968; 1 item
  - Case Institute of Technology. Research Abstracts., 1964; 1 item
  - Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique, 1950-1951; 15 items
  - Cerebral oxygen, n.d.; 2 items
  - Changes in cerebral oxygen tension produced by breathing mixtures of O2, CO2, and N2, 3 items
  - Chemical Warfare: Leimdorfer, Alfred. "About Anoxia of the Hear Produced by Intravenous Sodium-Cyanide-Injections", n.d.; 1 item
  - Chemical Warfare: Lipton, Barbara. "Case Report: Blocking of Chemical Decerebration by Pontile Pathology", n.d.; 1 item
  - Chemical Warfare: Olsen, Norman S. and J. Raymond Klein. "Effect of Cyanide on the Concentration of Lactate and Phosphates in Brain", 1 item
  - Chemical Warfare: Ward, Arthur A., Jr. "Convulsive Activity Induced by Fluoracetate", 1 item
  - Chemical Warfare: Ward, Arthur A., Jr. "Decerebrate Rigidity", n.d.; 1 item
  - Chemical Warfare: Ward, Arthur A., Jr. "Sodium Cyanide: Time of Appearance of Signs as a Function of the Rate of Injection", n.d.; 1 item
  - Chemical Warfare: Ward, Arthur A., Jr. and Max D. Wheatley. "Sodium Cyanide: Sequence of Changes of Activity Induced at Various Levels of the Central Nervous System", 1 item
  - Chemical Warfare: Wheatley, Max D. "Mechanism of Cerebral Death with Doses of NaCN from which the Heart Recovers", n.d.; 1 item
  - Chemical Warfare: Wheatley, Max D., Barbara Lipton, and Arthur A. Ward, Jr. "Repeated Cyanide Convulsions withough Central Nervous Pathology", 1 item
  - Chemical Warfare: Wheatley, Max D., and Warren S. McCulloch. "Sundry Changes in Physiology of Cerebral Cortex Following Rapid Injectin of Sodium Cyanide", 1 item
  - Chicago Heart Association, 1949; 4 items
  - Chicago Literary Club #1, 1942-1952; 14 items
  - Chicago Literary Club #2, 1953-1963; 13 items
  - Chicago Neurological Society, 1942-1952; 20 items
  - Civil Aviation Medical Association, 1966-1969; 3 items
  - Colliculo spinal paths, 1954; 3 items
  - Columbia Broadcasting System "Frontiers of Science", 1946; 1 item
  - Conference: AGARD meetings #1, 1965-1966; 20 items
  - Conference: AGARD meetings #2, 1965; 19 items